Good morning, good afternoon, good evening, ladies and gentlemen, it's been a while.
I'm Waka Yasumori from Inagi Town, Yasumori.
It's been a long time!
Yes, that's right, I've been waiting for a very long time!
Well, this is not a wasteland.
This is Yasumori Farm.
As a result of neglecting it for more than half a year, the weeds have been completed.
We are not growing something.
So, after a long time, I would like to reopen Yasumori Farm.
First of all, why am I reopening the farm?
There is a purpose.
We are going to have a barbecue at Tohoku-san.
At that time, even if it's just one thing...
I have to bring something from Yasumori Farm.
I won't be able to fulfill my duties as farm manager.
What do you say?
My duty.
Yes, I can't, so I'm going to take this opportunity to clean up the whole place and return the soil to a great condition, and although we only have a little time left, I'm going to do my best to grow vegetables.
Thank you for your patience, and today we will start with the cleanup.
What shall I do?
It's been a long time since I've worked on something like this.
Okay, I'm off.
Good night.
I'm almost done with the weeding, and I'm going to start with winter and the world.
A little while ago, I saw a little bit in the middle of here.
I found a potato about this size.
There was a caterpillar.
A caterpillar.
You know...
It's not a life style.
Around here...
I'll...
I'll let the staff do it.
Yes, sir.
I'll do my best on everything else.
My back hurts.my back hurts
I can't lose
Yes, I mean...
How many hours have passed since then?
It's already evening.
It's beautiful, isn't it? The evening of the Invinses.
It was a prairie until a few minutes ago.
Now it's so beautiful.
Look.
There's room for more!
Wow!
I've been waiting for you.
That feels good.
Right there on the edge.
There you are.
Yes, so it's so clean now.
There are some weeds that I haven't gotten rid of in some places.
I'm just going to bug out the big, rough weeds for now.
Also, the soil had been ruined for a while.
I mixed the soil with lime so that it can recover.
I will plant seedlings again after a while.
So we finished today's work.
Thanks to the staff's help, we now have a house!
Thank you very much!
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening.
I am Yasumori Waka, the farm manager of Yasumori Farm.
Yes, so last time I plowed the field that was a wasteland
I sprinkled lime and soil conditioner.
And now that I've taken a little bit
I'm going to finally plant vegetables from here!
I went to buy seedlings on the day I plowed the field.
Here's what I'm going to plant this time!
A mini-tomato!
But the weather has been too nice the last few days, so they got a little bit overgrown.
They're a little weak!I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I just gave it plenty of water.
I'm going to plant it again, hoping that it will get well again from here.
What kind is it?
Twinkle, Rung-chan's twinkle!
And also, a super sweet mini red.
I'd like to plant these two kinds.
Yes, and I bought one more kind.
Here it is. Ta-da!
It's a green shiso shiso leaf!
This one is a little bit weak.
I've given it plenty of water, so I'm going to plant it again, hoping it will be healthy again.
See you soon!
Well, I've finished planting them like this!
Since the tomatoes are quite tall, I already tied them to the poles like this.
It's really like the rainy season is over!
The weather has been so fine that the leaves have grown old or weakened more than I expected, but I will give them lots of water today.
I'm going to give them lots of water today.
I'm going to keep on dealing with the weather and praying that these mini-tomatoes will grow up!
This is how it looks here, too.
I wonder if they'll do well... I'm a little nervous.
But the flowers are blooming quite a bit around here, so I want to give them plenty of water and let them grow properly.
Tomatoes are like this.
And here are two plants of shiso leaves.
I don't really know how to grow shiso leaves.
I don't really know how to grow shiso leaves, but it says to harvest them when the leaves become fluffy and there are about 10 big leaves on them.
I learned that if the leaves are exposed to too much sun, they become hard.
So, I would like to cover the plants with a plastic sheet called "Kankou-kaiso," which is not a plastic to block out light.
Here is a cold checker.
This is an excellent product that can protect from storms and rain.
I would like to put this over the shiso leaves.
Yes, there are some big leaves in here, and I put the gauze over the support pole like this.
I think this will block out a lot of sunlight.
So, we have completed today's work.
Today, I introduced mini-tomato and shiso seedlings,
And plant them in the field.Then, they are planted in the field.
Then, I put the leaves on top of the leaves to prevent them from hardening,
The weather has been so nice for the past few days,
It was so hot like summer that I was wondering where the rainy season went,
The leaves were a little wilted, and I was worried,
But after giving it lots of water and exposing it to sunlight, it was getting better and better,
I think it will probably be all right.
I will continue to keep an eye on them and come back often to water them,
I will do my best to deliver delicious vegetables to everyone.
Good morning. Good morning. Good evening.
I am Waka Yasumori, the farm manager of Yasumori.
It has been about two weeks since we planted tomatoes and shiso leaves, and today I would like to show you how they are doing.
I would like to show you how things are going today, along with the age-old signboard. Let's take a look.
First of all, here are the shiso leaves. They have grown very large. Isn't it amazing? The number of leaves has increased a lot.
It smells a little like shiso. Amazing.
What do you get out of this?
You mean the leaves? Shiso leaves? That's what I'm talking about, right?
That's great. I think we're going to make it to the barbecue, so I'm going to keep looking at it.
It's going well. And here are the tomatoes. Look how big they've grown.
The tomatoes are turning a little orange-red. It's amazing.
I hadn't taken pictures in about two weeks, but I came here often to check on them and to water them, and they've grown so much. Look.
This is where I taped the top of the plant, and it has grown so much again. And the flowers are growing, too, so I hope they will grow in time for the barbecue.
The weather has been so nice lately, so I think they have changed color a little, but there are more fruits here.
They are looking good.
It's going to rain again, so I hope they'll do well, but I hope they'll make it in time.
The other day when I came here, there were fallen fruits, so I was wondering if birds had killed them again. The orange ones.
I put a net like this around the entire area to protect the berries, and it seems to be working well.
I hope they will continue to grow. So that's today's record.
Yay!
I'm not wearing any makeup, so I can't show you my face.
Good morning. Good morning. Good evening.
I'm Yasumori-waka, the young lady from Yasumori no En.
Great, delightful voice.
Yes, so today is the 8th of July. What day is it?
Yes, it is. Today is the day of 19-hour delivery.
Yes, I'm at E-Beans, everyone's favorite E-Beans in front of Sendai Station,Yes, I'm at E-Beans, everyone's favorite E-Beans in front of Sendai Station,
The reason why I am there,
I am going to harvest vegetables before that 19-hour delivery starts.
I'm trying to grow some delicious vegetables for everyone for today's 19-hour delivery,
I started growing tomatoes and shiso leaves in the middle of June,
When I came to see the vegetables yesterday, I found that they were bearing fruit and that I would be able to harvest a lot of shiso leaves,
I'd like to come and harvest them one step ahead of everyone else.
Let's go to the farm.
Here are the mini-tomatoes. They have grown bright red.
I was hoping to have 9 tomatoes since there are 9 members, but unfortunately, we can harvest 1, 2, 3, and 4, so I'd like to harvest 4 for now.
I'm going to harvest!
Seino
Oh!
Got it!
Wow!
Looks so good!
It's so red!
I'm so glad they grew so well.
I'm so happy!
It's going great!
I don't know, I didn't get them in time.
But I'm sure I'll be able to get more and more from here on out.
It's really something.
Yes!
Last one.
I think I'm almost done with this orange one.
Oh, it came off a little.
Okay, four!
Harvest is complete. If we'd started a little earlier, we probably would have gotten more.
Now let's go harvest the shiso leaves.
Look at the shiso leaves! They're growing so big!
They're perfect.
I'm going to harvest these too. This is my first shiso leaf.
It smells like perilla.
And here we go!
This looks like we're going to get a lot of leaves.Wow, this looks like we're going to get a lot. A lot of leaves!
That's a lot of leaves.
We're going to have a barbecue or something.
I'm planning to have a barbecue, so I'm thinking of wrapping them around meat and eating them.
We all love sisu.
I'm glad we made it in time for the distribution.
I wish we had started earlier.
If we'd started a little earlier, we could have picked a lot of cucumbers and peppers.
I'm sure we could have harvested a lot.
Isn't it amazing? You can harvest so many shiso leaves.
You can cook them, not just wrap them around meat.
Wow, a lot of shiso leaves!
Wow, it smells so good!
Oh, wow!
Wow, I got it!
Yes, so the harvest is complete!
Well, it looks like this!
We ended up with 24 shiso leaves and 4 tomatoes!
I was worried because I didn't know if they would really grow by today, because it had been less than a month.
But when the soil and other things died down, they grew up fine after all!
For the first time in a long time, I experienced the joy of growing vegetables!
I'm so happy!
I hope everyone is happy!
Everyone was really excited about the farm and asked me if I was going to do it. I'm so happy to be able to show the result like this.
I'm happy to be able to show the results like this!
Thank you very much for your support for the Farm Manager's Farm!
We're still growing tomatoes and shiso leaves, so...
I'm sure we'll keep growing tomatoes and shiso leaves and stuff.
If I can, I'd like to grow more vegetables.
I would like to work hard on the farm again this summer.
So please continue to support Yasumori Farm after this!
So, I'm off for a 19-hour delivery!
Bye bye!
I wonder what he's going to eat?
Yasumori-san's
Can I eat it as is? I've disinfected and washed it.Can I eat it as is? I've sterilized it. I've washed it.
We ate it, too.
I'll wrap it around the meat and eat it.
Thank you. - I'm hungry.
I'm hungry.
I'm not gonna eat it.
It's delicious.
It's expensive.
Is it good?
I'm glad.
Miyu has been feeding them to me for a while now.
Feeding experience!
I'm so happy!
Is it good?
I'm so glad!
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
It's so good!
I'm so happy.
It smells so good.
Really?
It's delicious.
Maybe I'll become a full-time farmer after all.
I'm not a full-time farmer.
I really don't.
I'm happier than I've ever been.
I don't know, I'm just... a little happier.
What?
I thought I should tell you.
But it makes me happy to hear you say it.
I'm not kidding.
It makes me happy.